http://www.navarrowine.com/policy/#privacy

You are:
myNavarro
Welcome Guest. (Sign In)
Returns and Refunds
Our policy is to refund or replace any wine or merchandise that is damaged, flawed, packed incorrectly or broken.
We request that if a bottle of wine is corked, you send us the cork.
We cannot accept a return of wine that was ordered in error or damaged by adverse weather conditions.
We make every effort to warn you of adverse weather in your area and give you the option of overriding a shipping delay at your own risk.
If you have a problem with a wine or other merchandise please email sales@navarrowine.com.
Terms and Conditions
We hope you enjoy this virtual visit to our Farm.
By browsing this website you are agreeing to the following terms of use:
This web site is for general information and use only and the information may change at any time.
We cannot guarantee the accuracy, timeliness and completeness of the information for any particular purpose and acknowledge that there may be inaccuracies or errors; these inadvertent errors exclude liability to the fullest extent permitted by law.
Navarro Vineyards’ website includes material, photos and design and reproduction is prohibited without express authorization.
We have occasional included links to other websites which we do not endorse of have no responsibility for their content.
Any disputes arising out of the use of Navarro Vineyards’ website is subject to the laws of the nation and states.
Alcoholic beverages require the signature of a sober person 21 or older and are for personal consumption and not for resale.
You may pay for your orders by credit cards including Visa, MasterCard and Discover as well as by check.
Your shipment will not be sent until payment has cleared.
When your wine or cheese order is picked up by UPS or any other shipper, the wine becomes the responsibility of the purchaser.
We recommend shipping to a business address during periods when the weather is neither too hot nor too cold, on the route to you.
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
Navarro Vineyards collects information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, or become a Pre-Release member.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing and billing addresses, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously but some features, such as placing orders, will be unavailable.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
; To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
; To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Opting out of email
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. You may alternatively opt out of all email marketing messages by sending an email to sales@navarrowine.com from the email address you wish to unsubscribe. Please clearly state in your email, "Unsubscribe me from future email." Your request will be processed in a timely manner. Once processed, your email address will no longer be used by Navarro Vineyards or shared with third parties.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, financials, etc.) will be removed from the website but kept on file in our tasting room in order to facilitate future orders or maintain Pre-Release membership.
Do we use cookies?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone, by fax, or by post.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
Some states require, by law, that Navarro Vineyards purchase a shipping permit, collect taxes where applicable, and then report sales information about wine shipments into the state. Select your state to see the specific information that we must provide.
Please select your state
AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettesMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyoming
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 21 years old or older.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. By purchasing wine, you consent that you are at least 21 years of age.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
This policy was last modified on January 17th, 2017.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
Navarro Vineyards (http://www.navarrowine.com)
P.O. Box 47 (mailing)
5601 Highway 128 (street)
Philo, CA 95466
(707) 895-3686 or sales@navarrowine.com
Navarro Vineyards is at 5601 Hwy 128, Philo, CA 95466 · Tasting Room hours: 9 AM to 6 PM Summer (5 PM Winter)
Sales, Shipping & Customer Service: 8 AM to 6 PM Summer (5 PM Winter) @ 1-800-537-9463 or 707-895-3686 · Fax: 707-895-3647
Copyright © 1997 - 2020 Navarro Vineyards. All Rights Reserved.
Privacy Policy ·Returns and Refunds · Terms of Service
